Today we'll try to break a board.
Our next move in board breaking: to position the board properly and to be able to break with a clean cut.
Okay?
Our next move, basically, coming down and take a look at the board.
Because it's a pine board, we have grains going down on the board and if you try to have those grains line up in a way, if you're doing a knife hand or you're doing a fist, it's lined up horizontally compared to our fist.
Our next step should be, make sure that the bricks are distanced proportionately.
There should be about half an inch cover on that board.
Okay?
Next step is positioning the body for it.
Our position for the next break which will be a fist, one board fist, is walking stance, which is about shoulder with a distance from the board.
You have to be able to go--move to the board and you have to be able to strike in a smooth movement.